## **CURRICULUM VITAE**

Mark Brian Kariuki

Mobile No: +254741242922

E-mail: kariukimarkbrian@gmail.com

## **Summary**

A 21-year-old computer science graduate with a certificate in Science Laboratory Technology from The Kabete National Polytechnic, and a certificate in Computer Applications from Digitech Computer College. Strong foundation in programming languages such as JavaScript, Python, and Ruby, as well as experience with software development methodologies such as Agile and Scrum. Demonstrates excellent communication and interpersonal skills, with a strong work ethic, adaptability, and commitment to learning and expanding his skill set.

# **Personal Details**

Date of Birth : 14/02/2001
Sex : Male
Nationality : Kenyan
Marital Status : Single
ID No. : 38601934
Religion : Christian

#### **Skills**

- Linux Administration
- Git
- Ruby on Rails
- React Js
- Node Js
- Heroku
- PostgreSQL
- MySQL
- HTML
- CSS
- Python
- Android Development

#### **Education**

May - Nov 2022

Moringa School

Software Engineering- Full-Stack Developer

2019 - 2021

The Kabete National Polytechnic

Certificate in Science Laboratory Technology

Jan – March 2018

Digitech Computer College

Certificate in Computer Applications

2014 - 2017

Kamuiru High School Kenya

Certificate of Secondary Education

2006 - 2013

Kiamutugu Junior Academy

Kenya Certificate of Primary Education

# **Work Experience**

March 2018 – December 2018

Cyber Cafe

Worked as a customer service representative

June 2020 – December 2020

Shoe Shop

Worked as a sales representative

February – Late March 2020

National Agricultural Research Laboratories

Industrial Attachment at the Soil Testing Department

January – April 2021

National Agricultural Research Laboratories

Industrial Attachment at the Soil Testing Department

## **Co-curricular Activities**

- Participated in Rugby and Catholic Association in Secondary School
- Member of the Drama Club and Red Cross Club in College

### **Hobbies and Interests**

Farming

- Reading novels
- Academic writing
- Script writing
- Community development
- Watching movies
- Hiking
- Traveling

# References

Madam Kamanda

H .O. D Science Laboratory Technology

The Kabete National Polytechnic

P.O Box 29010 - 00625

Tel: 0722384017

Faith Gathigia

Student Support Associate

Moringa School

P.O Box 28860 - 00100

Tel: 0713863008